#### **Komal R Sonar**

# sonarkomal10@gmail.com

Mobile No.: (+91) 9096568637

# **Career Objective:**

Knowledgeable & Motivated Business Analyst with comprehensive experience and understanding of business analysis & growth. Prioritize a strong attention to small details to ensure nothing is overlooked, integrating excellent communication techniques to make analysis information is always clean, clear & accurate.

### **Work Experiences:**

• Worked as an "Software Developer" at Supra InfoTech, Nasik.

**Designation: Software Developer** 

**Duration**: 8 Months

**Project name:** UStoUS (Hybrid Mobile application & Web App) https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=io.ionic.starterandroid&hl=en

### Scope of project:

US to US Mobile Application: This was built in Ionic & Angular 5. Us to US, a voluntary work organization, is an affiliate of the Saudi Arabian Cultural Mission to the United States. Us to US app for manage group activity, a voluntary work organization, is an affiliate of the Saudi Arabian Cultural Mission to the United States.

### Responsibilities

- Analysis of the Client Requirements and administration of the project.
- Active participation in the development phases of the project and Involved in coding of key areas and fixing the errors found during integration testing and Implementation.
- Currently working as, an "Business Analyst" at Supra InfoTech, Nasik.

Designation: **Business Analyst Duration**: 1st July 2018 to till date

### **Job Description**:

- Analyze client requirements & create bids & proposals

- Interact with client to know the complete requirements, provide technical perspective & elicit requirements
- Design the Wireframe & develop the requirement specification as per the template
- Collaborate with developers and solution team to establish the technical vision and analyze trade-offs between usability and performance needs
- Provide input in developing & modifying system to meet client's requirement
- Assist the Development team in developing & Maintaining relationship with clients.
- Promoted company's product by conducting market research & analysis.
- Working as an "HR & Administrator" at Supra InfoTech, Nasik.

**Duration**:1st July 2018 to till date

## Jobs & Responsibilities as an HR and Administrator:

- Recruitment of new staff & employees
- Fill up new joining form & assisting whole Recruitment
- Conducted campus drive at various college in Maharashtra.
- Maintain employee files & records in spreadsheets.
- Generated all types report (Absenteeism, Early Departure, Late Arrival, Etc.)
- Preparing monthly report in Attendance System
- Generate costing report. Preparing Salary and Wages.

## **Core competencies:**

- Listening skills
- Good communication skills
- Strong organization skills and ability to work under pressure & to a deadline.
- Business system enhancement
- Team handling & Leadership
- Business plan development
- Website content development

## **Recent Achievements/Bidding & Projects Won:**

- 1. Word Press Expert to Build A Website
- 2. Developer needed for creating a Responsive WordPress website
- 3. Dynamic landing page
- 4. Web Portal UIUX
- 5. Need to finish a website adding some map functions.
- 6. Help integrate Mailchimp WP Plugin & Google Analytics Goal Tracking
- 7. PHP proficient and API developer

# **Technical Proficiency:**

• Languages: C, C++, Java, Android

• Databases: MYSQL, SQLite.

• Operating System: Windows 7, Windows XP, Windows 10, Linux

## **Educational Qualification:**

Degree	University	Marks
BE (Computer)	Pune Board	65.93% (Distinction)
Diploma(Computer)	Pune Board	63.36% (First Class)
S.S.C	State Board	79.40% (Distinction)

#### **Achievements:**

- Secured 2<sup>nd</sup> Rank in Group presentation Competition held by NDMVP, Nasik
- Secured 2<sup>nd</sup> Rank in Quiz-Brainstorm held in MET, Nasik (2012)

### **Co-curricular Activities:**

- I was instrumental in Conducting "Supra Campus Drive Recruitment" at K.V.N. Naik College of Engineering, Nasik.
- Worked as Ladies Representative of SMES Polytechnic, Nasik.(2012-13).
- Supra InfoTech was represented in Mahindra Job Utsav-2019 at Guru Gobind Singh College.
- Actively participated to promoting & Marketing of Company products. (CCA Marketing at college level)

#### **Additional Skills:**

- Proficient in Microsoft office (Word, Excel, Power point)
- Familiarity with Agile software development methodology
- Familiar with BRD, FRD, Use Cases etc.

#### **Personal Details:**

• **Birth Date** : 19 December 1994.

• Marital Status : Single.

• Languages known: Read/Write/Speak-English, Hindi, Marathi.

I hereby declare that the above written particulars are true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

